http://www.gebco.net/privacy_policy/

Gridded bathymetry data
Regional grid - Arctic Ocean (IBCAO)
Regional grid - Southern Ocean (IBCSO)
Gridded bathymetry data
Regional grid - Arctic Ocean (IBCAO)
Regional grid - Southern Ocean (IBCSO)
GEBCO privacy notice
GEBCO's web site is hosted and maintained by the British Oceanographic Data Centre (BODC), National Oceanography Centre, United Kingdom.
Personal data
Contact List
GEBCO maintains an email contact list of people who have expressed an interest in receiving updates on GEBCO projects and activities. Your email contact will only be used by GEBCO to update you on GEBCO activities. We will not share or on sell your email contact to 3rd parties. GEBCO will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal data from loss, misuse or alteration.
To unsubscribe from the mailing list contact the Seabed 2030 Global Center:
Website usage
BODC collects standard internet log information and anonymous details of visitor behaviour patterns. The former enables us to troubleshoot problems and the latter to improve the speed of our service and enhance your experience.
Through the GEBCO web site, BODC does not capture or store any personal information that can be used to identify an individual. However, for the purposes of downloading data from GEBCO's gridded data sets you will be re-directed to BODC's web site and need to provide some personal information in order to register to access the data sets. Please see BODC's web site privacy and cookies information.
Cookies
What are cookies?
When web sites provide services, they want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally.
These pieces of information are used to improve services for you through, for example:
Enabling a service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task.
Recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page requested.
Measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there's enough capacity to ensure they are fast.
GEBCO's web site only uses cookies as described in category 3. Find out more about cookies from AboutCookies.org.
Our use of cookies
Our cookies cannot be used to collect personally identifiable information about you. Please be aware that restricting cookies may ultimately impact on the services we provide.
Essential cookies
These first-party cookies enable us to improve the response of our service.
Name
Expiration
Purpose
sessionid
browser exit
These cookies are used by our server load balancing switch. This enables us improve our service by managing and maintaining users sessions.
userid
Persists
Cookies for improving service
We use Google Analytics to monitor visitor behaviour patterns. Google Analytics uses first-party cookies as described below to track visitor interactions.
First-party cookies are not shared by browsers across domains. For more information see an overview of Google's policies and principles.
Name
Expiration
Purpose
_utma
2 years
Google Analytics cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. They consist of a randomly generated number. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, for example the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. We use this information to target development activities to help us improve the site and to compile reports.
_utmb
30 minutes
_utmc
browser exit
_utmz
6 months
How to control cookies
If you wish, you can control which cookies are
set on your device, using your browser settings. The 'Help' function within your browser should tell you how.
Alternatively, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org, which contains comprehensive information on how to allow, block, delete and manage cookies on a variety of browsers.
Within your browser you can also view the cookie code; simply click on a cookie to open it. You will see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are the identification card and can only be seen by the server that set the cookie and yourself.
For information on how to manage cookies on the browser of your mobile phone you will need to refer to the handset manual.
